FLAVIEN CHAMAY | APPLICATION ANALYST

Hi. I'm a Tech and Math enthusiast who lived in Canada and Europe. I speak/write French and English, have experience in Python, Bash and Linux administration. I did a 3 months training on DevOps and have 2 years of professional experience at Capgemini.



CONTACT

flavien.chamay@protonmail.com

Toulouse, France

github.com/flavienChamay

IT SKILLS

Programming Languages

Python Java **SQL Bash LaTeX**

Operating Systems

Linux Manjaro | Ubuntu Linux Debian | RHEL Windows 10



Software & Tools

GitHub/Git **Emacs** Vim **Technologies**

Docker

Languages English B2 grade **Native French**



INTERESTS

A.I., Extraterrestrial life, Mathematical logic, Hacking.

PROJECTS

- Web Blog (Django, Heroku, Personal project in progress).
- Simple Blockchain (Python, Personal project finished): coding of the proof of work, the wallet and data encryption.
- Tic-Tac-Toe Game (Python, Personal project in progress): Minimax algorithm for computer player, CLI interface, save/load mechanisms.
- Planning by satisfiability of logical formulas (Touist, Internship(3 months)): coding, modeling and benchmarking of logic problem solving A.I..
- NeoCampus, real-time sensors (Java, Academic project): GUI coding and data re-
- Caesar encryption (C, Academic project): encryption/decryption of text files.

WORK HISTORY

2021 - present

Capgemini France Blagnac & Toulouse, France

2017 - 2020

Auterive & Toulouse, France

April 2011 - August 2011

Staples Quebec, Canada **Application Analyst** in GED applications (Alfresco, Libriciel) for electronic signatures

Tutor for private lessons in Maths and C.S.

Computer Repairman & **IT Consultant**

EDUCATION

iuly 2021 - september 2021

♀ IB - Cegos Formation Toulouse, France

2017 - 2020

Paul Sabatier University Toulouse, France

2011 - 2016

Paul Sabatier University Toulouse, France

DevOps & Networks Consultant

Computer Science Bachelor Degree

1st & 2nd cycle in Physics 2nd cycle in Maths

GENERAL SKILLS

Model/specify/integrate/maintain/develop an app Assess client's need Analyse origin of malfunction Identify/protect confidential data

Understand/write doc. in Eng/Fr

HOBBIES & OCCUPATIONS

